Visit turkision.com for more!
Holofira!
Holofira, open your eyes come on.
Holofira.
-I hope she never opens her eyes.
-Shut it, Hatun!
Enough, get out Elcim. Come on, out.
You, how did you learn about the crusaders?
This is my land. I know
everything going on in here.
Who are you? Who are you
to sneak around in my lands?
-Who?
-Do not be so sure.
-You will find out who I am.
-First..
..first, you will tell me where the
crusadery army will come from.
You will learn it by living through it with pain.
Your people will be crushed in front of your eyes.
The person who will teach
you is right in front of you!
So you are serious.
The only reason why I do not
kill you right here and now..
..is because you know where my signs are.
All your loved ones will
die in front of your very eyes.
You will come to me begging.
Turahan.
Turahan, my brother.
Quick, inform the others..
..they took the captives to Sahin Hill.
-Okay, Cerkutay Bey.
-Come on brother.
These dogs attacked my
caravan. They killed Uraz Bey.
Let us attack. Let us break
these dogs, what's the hold up?
You will not be Osman’s death today.
You fall back when I go far enough.
Where are you running to?
Clear each of my weak men, Osman.
Where are these dogs heading to?
Clashing sounds come from the tribe.
They are attacking Osman Bey. Alps, come on!
You should've let me kill her, Bala Hatun.
Holofira attacked my aunt.
What do you mean killing?
What did you do Elcim Hatun?
You do not know Holofira.
She doesn't do such a thing!
-This hatun blinded all of you.
-Enough, Elcim...
You are acting without thinking.
Go have some air.
You do more harm than good here.
Kismet, close the door for Allah's sake!
Mother, Gonca help me.
-Have her smell this.
-Alright.
My Allah, do not test me with such pain.
Thank Allah, we are blessed.
The dagger hit the necklace.
My Allah, thank you.
-Orhan.
-I am here
I am here, my Holofira. Do not worry.
-Are you alright, my girl?
-I am alright, thank you.
Alright then.
Sisters...
Sisters, take Holofira
and Olivia to prison.
I will question them.
They will stay in the cells...
...until the truth is revealed.
Neither me nor Holofira did anything.
-Sisters, come on.
-Holofira, say something
-Mother..
-Enough Orhan, I said what I said.
-My Bey, are you alright?
-I am alright.
-It was obvious this dog set you up.
-Let him set as many traps as he wants!
Now, he wants the relics of Seljuks.
He says he will be on us
unless we give them up. Just wait.
First, he will give me what I want.
Konur, you will send alps after that dog Imren.
I want to know about those passages.
-As you command, my Bey.
-We will be on his neck.
-Of course we will not let that dog go.
-What about the crusaders issue?
-What does he say to that?
-This is the dog that made the deal possible.
However, we do not have much time.
Crusader army is coming towards us.
That is why I will go to
Atranos. I will talk to that dog.
My Bey, they will do worse at the castle.
Pope and Olcaytu wants to unite and crush us.
-Of course we will not allow it.
-It seems..
...horses will gallop and grass will be crushed.
Do not worry, Gunduz Bey. We are not grass.
Thank Allah, we are a mighty tree. And
we have a thousand year old roots here.
That is why, we are the owner
of the tribe. We are the hunters.
Those dogs are the one that
should be afraid. Everyone, to horses.
They can not hide that many
women and children I think.
Brother, the forest thickens ahead.
There must be places to hide.
Let us check it out now.
-Solgur Aga!
-Yes, Turahan.
They took the captives at the road to Sahin Hill.
Cerkutay Bey went ahead.
Let me go after them. Maybe I will find tracks.
Solgur Aga. Now, we need to be sneaky.
They call me "The Lion Hunter".
I know how to be sneaky..
..and claw my enemies!
Praise be to you!
Brothers, this duty is important.
-We need to be there quick.
-Come on then!
Now!
O Allah!
Allah is the greatest!
Father! Father! Father!
If he is even slightly harmed...
...I will make you drown in your own blood.
Come. Come here, my boy. My son!
Praise be, praise be!
-Don't be afraid.
-It's alright. It's alright.
It's alright, my boy. You are good. You are good.
Orhan Bey.
I said you'd be in trouble
as long as she stayed in the palace.
-And what did you do?
-What did you do, hatun?
Ha? I told you. I trust
Holofira as much as I trust you.
Holofira you trust so much poisoned my aunt!
My aunt is dying, Orhan
Elcim Hatun!
I keep silent because I know this
impertinence of yours is due to your grief.
But you should know my patience has limits.
Your lover attempted to take my life.
-And you say...
-Holofira didn't do that!
Whoever did this, I will find her.
And you will apologize to Holofira.
Apologize?
-That girl bewitched you!
-Enough!
Orhan! Elcim!
Pull yourselves togethe You are in the palace.
Holofira didn't do such a thing.
-Investigate this.
-Just think about your duty, Orhan Bey.
Stay safe.
Investigate this, mother.
Let's go!
Come on!
You calm down, Elcim Hatun.
Don't let anger blind you.
I'm not the blind one, but Orhan Bey is.
Love blinds him. He doesn't see the truth.
The truth has many faces, girl.
Orhan accepted marrying you
for his state despite his love.
He wouldn't have done that if love blinded him.
If it is Holofira who did that...
...he will punish her himself.
She bewitched Orhan Bey.
Orhan Bey won't follow justice, but his love.
It's you who should listen to reason
before Orhan.
Anger has overwhelmed you. You can't use your mind.
Control your anger, girl.
I want no other mistakes.
-My Bey.
-Cerkutay.
-We took the captives.
-Thank you, Cerkutay.
Thank you. Thanks to Allah.
You did a great job.
Thanks to the alps' bravery.
Alright. Tell them we will
give each one a house and a job.
And we will meet all their
expenses. Tell them this too.
-As you order, my Bey!
-Sorgun Agha.
-Yes, my Bey?
-We will make Uraz tribe great again.
Alps have started the preparations.
Even no birds will fly over it.
If the flying bird is not one of us,
we will break his wings, for sure.
Come on, alps? Come on!
Son, she keeps sweating. She
also puked. But she's not going better.
The poison is in her blood, mother.
We need to find the cure quickly.
But I can't find the cure without
knowing what the poison is.
I'm going out.
You stay with her.
I know Holofira.
She wouldn't do that. She would
never betray you, Bala Hatun.
People sometimes may do
what doesn't suit them, Gonca.
I didn't expect you to do it either.
You're right, Bala Hatun.
But not every family is like you.
I said only one word to silence my mother,
...to prevent her from doing worse.
And I lost too much with one word.
Holofira may have been deceived as well.
-Her aunt may have used her, ha?
-Maybe.
People can't choose their mother or families.
But your children are really lucky. They
have their mother who always support them.
My mother became her own power's slave, Bala Hatun.
She even used her own children for this.
She even left her child alone.
The important thing
is to be able to see the
mistake and give up on
the wrong way, my daughter.
You are afraid of taking after your mother, right?
Don't worry. Everything is here.
If you keep this clean, you won't be like her.
Look Holofira... I know you didn't do this.
You are not a person who would kill someone.
Thus, you must tell me the things you know.
Why are you still silent? Tell
her that you are innocent! Speak!
Holofira... You are making it harder, my daughter.
You didn't do this, right?
You are also saying it, Malhun
Hatun. Holofira would not do this.
-You put us in dungeon for no reason.
-Then you speak, Olivia.
Holofira didn't do it, you
didn't do it, who did it then?
This is your palace.
You must know that.
You never trusted us since we
arrived. You locked us in a room.
We only got out with your sisters. Tell me...
How could I poison that woman?
But Holofira went out.
Sisters were also with her. How
could she go to Elcim's room?
I don't believe Holofira did this.
But I will never trust you... If
you are the one who did this...
...I won't forgive the one
who shed blood in my
palace, and I will take
your life with my own hands.
Malhun Hatun.
I want to talk to Dervish Efendi.
Orhan Bey... He knows him.
Yunus Emre?
Demirbogan, Baysungur, hurry.
The cart will come from this
way. They won't go anywhere.
Don't worry, my Shahzade.
We will make them see hell.
-Come... Come.
-Come on.
-Oghuz Alp.
-My Shahzade. -Together.
Come on.
Nokers! Nokers!
Come on! O Allah!
All nokers will be killed! Kill everyone,
except for the commander!
Insolent Turk who attacked
Great Olcaytu Khan's caravan...
...you will beg me not to kill you!
From now on, you will think
twice before you threaten a Turk.
And let this be a lesson for you.
Good... We have e gold. Baysungur.
Tie this dog, apparently, he has things to tell us.
You cannot make me speak!
I can strangle you here, shut up.
Come on! Take him!
Stand up! Come here!
Welcome, my Bey...
Malhun...
What happened?
What is the situation?
Ayca Hatun..
...was poisoned. -What?
Osman Bey?
Who did this?
We put Holofira and Olivia in the dungeon,
my Bey. We have doubts about them.
Osman Bey...
I thought putting them in the
dungeon was the best way to...
...calm Gunduz Bey and Elcim Hatun down.
You thought well. You
thought well. But... how is she?
Alaeddin is trying... He said he can
find the cure if he can find the poison.
What if he can't find it?
Did Holofira..
...say something?
She does not speak, my Bey. She
didn't answer to any of our questions.
What do you think?
Her test is not easy.
Even if I say the devil tricked her...
I don't think Holofira would do this.
-Father..
-My daughter...
I don't know who to be worried about.
My brother... The situation my brother is in...
What kind of test is this?
-Whom will he be upset for, huh?
-Don't worry, my daughter.
With Allah's consent, the one
who did this will be punished.
But we will pray for my Ayca daughter now.
Justice will handle the rest.
If we don't handle this matter justly...
...the unification of the Kayi
tribes will remain a dream for us.
The one who wanted this to
happen must have planned this.
We know who did it. Imren Tegin.
He was saying that he would chase us
like a nightmare unless he took the trusts.
This is only the beginning.
Let's see what else is going to happen.
We will solve this matter with justice.
And we will be careful if Allah permits.
We won't let it happen again.
Right... right. Come on.
My daughter... -Father!
-My daughter...
-How is Ayca?
-I told Orhan Bey.
That girl would hurt us.
I told him that blood would
be shed. He didn't listen, father.
We won't find peace until the one
who did this to my aunt is punished.
She will be punished, my daughter. Be patient.
Don't get up in anger and sit down
with a loss. I trust Osman Bey's justice.
This marriage will put us in trouble.
That Hatun cast a spell on Orhan Bey.
Father... father, let's give up.
Enough, Elcim
I don't care about what Orhan thinks, I
care about what Osman Bey is going to do!
He will surely punish the one who tried to kill...
...my daughter and poisoned my daughter-in-law.
Osman has learned that he is not
only fighting against Byzantium...
...but also against the Papacy and European states.
He will make a move. Be careful.
I don't understand how Osman learned this.
No one knew this except for that loose-tongued
Mongol dog who brought the trusts.
He must've told him.
What are we going to do? Osman
will make a move to defeat you.
He might. I will show him that it is impossible.
He won't be able to resist.
Imren Tegin... The Papacy, Latin,
and Frankish ambassadors have arrived.
They are waiting at the inn near
Harmanustu because of the siege.
Good... Right on time.
Bring them in through the secret passages.
You will burn in the hell of Crusaders, Osman.
Then I will establish my state
and turn that hell into my heaven.
Now I'm asking you nicely, commander.
You will take the gold to
Imren Tegin, we know that.
But Atranos is under our siege.
You can't take it * there. Now tell me,
Where are you going to meet with Imren Tegin?
You haven't experienced
the Olcayto Khan’s wrath yet
will herd you all like sheep, will here
You will herd us like a sheep, is that so?
You talk just like Tacettin Noyan, commander.
This is how you talk, this kind
of talking will take you to death.
I’m asking you for the last time,
where are you going to meet with
Imren's men, and when?
Do not resist, commander. Or I'll tie the
rope around your neck, not your hands.
Tell me, when and where?
Stop, stop!
That's it.
Now, talkCome on.
Imren Tegin's men will take the
gold from us in Karadere area.
How do I know that you're
telling the truth, commander?
It is written in the compass.
He's telling the truth. Untie him.
This is for our Muslim brothers you murdered.
The...
...Righteous!
Ignobles!
My Shahzade.
Then we need to go back to Yenisehir.
But I see that you don't want to return.
How can I, Baysungur? My palace
is now my hell. Elcim Hatun blames Holofira.
But Holofira cannot even hurt an ant.
The truth is like a sun, my Shahzade.
-It does not hide.
-Right.
I need to find a way to acquit Holofira.
But if I can't, then...
If Holofira is innocent,
it will be revealed eventually, my Shahzade,
but if she's guilty, what
Osman Bey will do is clear.
That's what I'm afraid of, Baysungur.
Allah is great. Come on.
I united Mongols and Papacy.
I gave Quds to the Crusaders.
The Crusaders army...
...is coming from Franks, Latins and Papacy.
They will storm into these lands
with the ships of Venetians.
They will unite with Byzantium.
Turks are holding the border lines.
Where are we going to come out?
From Sudibi.
Turks will want to unite against
this army, they will be equipped.
They will probably stand behind Kayis,
...the most resilient among them.
Which is Osman.
Osman knows that this army will crush his people
and loot them.
He will do whatever it takes
for us to cross Crusaders' lands.
His lands will make him time for defense.
It will waste our time, Imren Tegin.
But I won't let that happen.
I'll go with the pioneer troops
I'll destroy him before he sets his defense line.
In the name of Jesus Christ, Osman will
be destroyed just like the Seljuk Sultans.
We will set up headquarters
in Konya after Yenisehir.
In the meantime, the Crusader army that
will set out after the news of Osman's death
will have landed in Sudibi coast.
They will kill the Turks and come to Konya
then we'll go together
and we will take Quds.
And I will the only ruler of these lands.
Let's eat. You've come a long way.
You must be starving.
Of course we will not let Crusaders
cross our path, it's not a public inn.
No. Never. We will never let that happen.
Brave men will not move as a single army.
They will be under Beys' commands. And from now on
alps will only use hit and run tactics.
My Bey, I think we need to send scout units...
...in case Crusaders come via ship.
My Bey, it's not so hard to understand,
mren Tegin wants to destroy us using the Crusaders.
The Crusader army is like a swarm of locusts.
They want to crush us and then go to Konya.
We know what they did to their
fellow believers in Constantinople.
Who knows what will they do to us?
Imren Tegin does not only want our lands.
He also wants all the lands from the Frontier
Marketplace to the center of Kutahya.
So, tell me, Mehmed Bey.
What is needed to stop the Crusaders?
A lot of men and swords.
Let me tell you what you want
to hear, being united is needed.
Good, good.
You know us very well.
Know that I want you and your father behind me.
My father Yakup Bey is fighting in
the south. I can't ask soldiers from him.
If it is about being
united, I'll inform my father...
...and I'll support you
with the soldiers here.
Thank you.
Konur. Send messengers to Karesi, Candar,
Hamidoglus, Esrefoglus, all of them.
I want them all to support me in the battle.
Yes, my Bey.
There's no need to inform Candaroglus.
He already went to Kutahya,
his men must be fighting now.
What's he doing in Kutahya?
You ask for union, but we have
the same purpose, Alaeddin Bey.
The brother of Suleyman Bey, the Candaroglu Bey
and my sister Gonca Hatun will get married.
Candaroglu and I are practically in-laws.
Very well.
-I hope it works out well.
-Father.
This is needed for unity.
No one should stand against this unity.
Or they would pay the price heavily.
If there is nothing else to
be said, this council is over.
My Shahzade, Holofira Hatun..
..does not want to see you.
Holofira, so you do not want to talk to me.
Everyone blames you. However, L..
..I believe you, Lord's daughter.
You did not do this.
You did not poison her, I know.
And I will prove that to everyone.
How can father do this without
asking me about this first!
What will he ask about, Gonca? My
father and mother wants it, so will you.
am the one getting married,
not my mother or father!
You will do this for our tribe.
If you still think about Alaeddin,
you will not see him again.
You know what will happen if
you do. You are engaged now!
Are we allowed, Gonca Hatun?
Come in, Fatma.
Mother Bala calls you. They
need your help for Ayca Hatun.
-Go, Gonca.
-Alright, I will.
Alaeddin Bey.
-If you see my brother..
-Forget about your brother, Gonca!
Where did this marriage come
from? I try to keep calm after hearing it.
Did you know of it?
-No, I did not.
I am confused, Alaeddin.
My father..
How can my father do this
to me? I do not understand.
There is nothing to be confused.
It is apparent what to be done.
What is it?
We will get married.
Do you hear what you are saying?
Do you know what this means,
Alaeddin? This means war..
-..of Kayi and Germiyanids but also Candaroglu!
-If it means war..
..then I will fight, Gonca.
However, I will not let anyone have you.
-I will not.
-Alaeddin.
Your life is at the stake at the end of this.
I can not do this to you. I
can not throw you into the fire.
My Gonca. If you go, I will already fall in it.
Do not do this. Let us go to
my father, he will be on our side.
No.
Ask everything from me, even my life.
However, I can not throw you
into this fire Scholar, please.
You are calling me Scholar.
Is this how you would free
my name, Trickster Hatun?
Don't.
Say yes, and let this torture end.
If she says yes, I will be in trouble.
If she does not, I will still be in trouble.
Either way, I get into trouble.
O, Yakup Bey.
-Kanyumaz, we will head to Frontier Marketplace.
-My Shahzade?
-You go first with the goods tomorrow.
-As you command, my Shahzade.
No, they will get caught.
-Gonca.
-Mehmed will kill Gonca.
What will I do?
Get yourself into trouble Ghazi.
-All this for you, Gonca Hatun.
Mehmed Bey!
Draw youf sword and face me!
I am very mad at you!
So you want training, Ghazi Alp.
Come on theni
Valiant Ghazi!
You little valiant!
So you will defeat me, huh?
When am I going to
go to battle with you?
Do not ask this from me, Alaeddin.
Think about it until tomorrow morning, Gonca.
Think about it well.
I can not breathe without you, Hatun.
Holofira does not say a word, my
Bey. She only wants to see Yunus Emre.
Do not worry.
Yunus Emre will make her talk, I hope.
And we will find who did this.
I hope so, my Bey.
-Are we allowed, Osman Bey?
-Come in, Gunduz Bey.
Gunduz Bey, tell me. How is Ayca Hatun?
My bride, fights for her life in front of my eyes.
While she is in this state..
..how is the person who did this to her doing?
We are investigating Gunduz Bey. We
will find who is responsible, if Allah permits.
Isn't the person who did
this, is your son's lover..
..Holofira, Malhun Hatun?
-Or, are you afraid of someone?
-Hold it.
Hold it, Gunduz Bey. Who
have we ever been afraid of?
Tell me, who?
We are trying...
...to reveal the truth. To provide justice.
Thnak you.
Osman Bey...
...I trust your justice.
My Beys, my tribe are waiting for your word.
However, if the opposite happens..
..and balance is not provided..
So, Gunduz Bey?
-Complete your sentence.
-Then..
..I can not provide unity.
If I lose respect from my tribe, my beys..
..we will be gone, Osman Bey.
Osman Bey's justice does not
make mistakes, Gunduz Bey.
Do not worry.
There will be a court
tomorrow. Holofira will be judged.
If she is guilty, she will pay the price.
Don't you worry.
-Thank you.
-Malhun....
...hold her until tomorrow.
-As you command, my Bey.
Come on girls. You got the olives and bread?
Take the breads as well.
Come on ladies.
Come on then.
Mubarak Ramazan has arrived!
Your time has arrived as well.
I prayed so much during your absence, Cerkutay.
Thanks to Allah, we will
spend this Ramadan together.
We expelled dark times! Now we will be together!
My Ulgen, just tell me to smile...
...and our joy will be forever!
-Don't make me feel ashamed.
-Feel ashamed, girl.
Well... The drum has shown up, huh?
Alps didn't give me that for long.
They told me to grow up first.
I've grown up now. Give it to me.
Well, Ghazi... Your father...
...is the inventor of this drum.
It isn’t an easy job.
I never demand the easy.
-Wow.
-Look at him.
Just give it to him.
Let's see if he can.
Yes, Cerkutay Bey. I've seen him.
Ghazi has been waiting for
this moment for a long time.
You think he can do it?
Come on then.
Come here.
Take this. This one too.
Now hit it!
But only drum sound isn't enough.
We need nice words as well.
Everybody should jump up when they hear the words!
-I know words to say, father.
-Well...
Just watch the party now.
Brother.
Alaaddin.
Brother, Turkmen Bey will get mad
whe I run away with Gonca, right?
Things will be crazy. But if you.
don't, you will be burned, Alaaddin.
I will talk to father first.
But I don't know what to
do if he doesn't back me up.
What happened to us? My grandfather used to say...
"Love test would be tough."
As the love grows bigger, the tests gets harder.
I was feeling sorry for myself but
you fell into the same fire with me.
I don't know what we should do.
The state on one side.
And the woman I love on the other.
What's worse, she's in the dungeon.
With a broken and upset heart.
Her body...
...and my heart are in the dungeon.
Me? What should I do? She's
on the other end of this corridor.
If I went out in the corridor,
I could hear her breathing.
But I can't reach her.
I can't get close to her, brother.
Now there is also this marriage issue.
Brother, you should talk to father first.
If you can't find a way out, then...
Drumstick is short! Shahzade is tall...
...with a short mind.
I won't let you marry Gonca now get up for sahur!
Run away with her. I support you.
Even Ghazi alps tells you to run away with her.
Alaaddin, my brother...
Whatever you do, I will back you up.
Brother, I wouldn't hesitate for a moment
if I were Shepherd Osman's son but...
We are Bey Osman's son,
Yes. Yes. Bey Osman is
awaiting us for the sahur. Let's go.
Ramadan has arrived in our city!
And Rosebuds blossomed in our house!
Wake up for sahur!
Let the blessing rain over us!
Ramadan is Sultan of eleven months!
I have Gonca Sultan in my heart.
O Gonca, marry Ghazi Alp
So we can have double bairams in Ramadan!
Ghazi...
Come here, Ghazi.
-Keep playing it. Not everybody woke up.
-Tall Shahzade...
...has no authority on me!
I’m highly grateful to Allah who
let us reach this Ramadan Month.
If Allah permits, we will spend
this Ramadan in our tribe.
-If Allah permits.
-If Allah permits, my Bey.
Actually, I was thinking...
-We should hold the wedding there.
-It's appropriate.
Well...
You all know about the trouble over us.
But with this Ramadan Month, Allah...
...will give us strength to repel the heathens.
-Amen.
And we're making plans to keep
our people and Muslims united.
We will never let heathens get into our lands.
But remember this.
We need to provide unity for this first.
-Am I right, Gunduz Bey?
-Of course you are, Osman Bey.
Tell me, Mehmed Bey.
While heathens sharpen their teeth for us,
...we should stand stronger together.
When they attempt to bite us,
their teeth will get broken first.
Alright, Osman Bey.
We will always do our part.
Thank you, thank you.
Konur.
Did the alps in the castle of Atronos get paid?
-We prepared all in the morning, my Bey.
-Thank you, thank you.
We also handed out the food to
Yenisehir people for Ramadan, my Bey.
And we made up all the
shortages of Gunduz Bey's people.
Thank you, live long.
Thank you.
"He who sleeps with a full stomach while his
neighbor is hungry is not a true believer"
...our Prophet said.
They are not our neighbors,
but members of my house.
Now we’re even responsible for the food in
the throat of the bird flying over the mountain.
If we find a piece of bread, we should share it.
Now that our people have soup today...
....let's get started then. In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
May our sahur be mubarak.
Let's start, let's eat.
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
Father, playing the drum made me hungry.
Eat, my boy.
Here, Osman.
Imren Tegin. I will bury you
alive in the castle of Atronos...
...where you are hiding.
Allah is with us.
You will see, Imren Tegin.
-Do I have permission, my Bey?
-Come in.
My Bey, you wanted to see us?
Welcome. Welcome. Here we are.
In the name of Allah,
the merciful, the compassionate.
If this can! heal her, it will be very hard to
save Ayca Hatun from the death dungeon.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate. Help us, my Allah.
I've found it! Thanks to Allah, I’ve found it!
Baysungur!
-Osman Bey, this is a dangerous move.
-We don't have any other chance, Bala Hatun.
If we fail, everyone in our
lands will become our enemies.
We will risk everything, Malhun Hatun.
We will risk everything.
This is not only for our lands.
This is for the lands of all Turks.
That's how we can protect Yakup
Bey's lands and the well-being of Turks.
Thus, Konur...
You will arrest Germiyan Alps
without shedding their blood.
You will gather them in Kizilca cave.
Yes my Bey.
-What about Mehmet and Gonca?
You will lock them in a room in the
palace. They will not leave the palace.
And we will take the frontiers marketplace.
What about Yakup Bey? What will he say to this?
Hard decisions are made during hard times.
We cannot waste time by telling this to anyone.
-Tell me, is everyone ready for the hearing?
-Yes my Bey.
Okay, okay. If we cannot secure justice...
...today in the hearing...
...it won't be good for Turks' well-being.
If Holofira tried to kill Ayca Hatun...
...she will be punished.
-What if it's not her who did this?
Then we will have to convince Gunduz Bey.
And that will be difficult. But no matter what...
...we will secure the justice.
-Can I come in, my Bey?
-Come in.
My Bey, Alaeddin Bey sent this.
-This is Olivia's ring, my Bey.
-Olivia...
There was poison in it, my Bey. It was used.
Olivia...
-Boran.
-My Bey...
You will present this as evidence in the hearing.
Yes my Bey.
Now we will walk to Atranos.
Then we will set our court.
Now it is time to face Imren.
-Boran. -My Bey.
-Prepare the horses.
-Yes my Bey.
-Justice...
...will be secured in the palace
and in the castle of the infidels.
If we cannot find the poison, my
aunt will die in front of us, father.
Don't give up hope, my daughter.
Alaeddin Bey is going to heal.
Justice will be secured, if Allah permits.
I don't trust the fairness of this hearing, father.
Elcim! Don't you know me, my daughter?
The one who tried to hurt someone
from my family will be punished’
-I will not let them decide otherwise!
-I hope so, father.
I hope it will happen as you say.
-Can I come in, Gunduz Bey?
-Come in, Alaeddin Bey.
Did you find the poison, Alaeddin Bey?
This is my last hope.
-I hope this will heal.
-If Allah permits -Make her drink this.
In the name of Allah, the merciful,
the compassionate.
O Healer, O Healer, O Healer!
Imren Tegin... Osman.
He came to Atranos to talk to you.
He can come. I was waiting for him.
It must've been hard
for him to wait for death...
...in his own land, since he
came to his own Azrael
He trusts the signs he has.
He might bow down and give you back the trusts...
People like Osman do not bow down easily, Daniel.
He will want to bargain for sure.
Let's kill him. Then he and Turks will have seen...
...how we bargain. Then,
they will also bring the trusts.
Torment or death won't make Osman step back.
He will live until I take the things I want, then..
...then Turks...
...and Osman will die.
Let’s go.
Let's see the inside of...
...the Atranos Castle that we besieged.
Look very carefully, it will be your last time.
I can see that your wounds were healed.
Nothing is heavier than what you lost, Imren Tegin.
Your men cannot be beaten
in a quarrel, right, Osman?
If you're here to see my castle, come on.
I'll show you my brave warriors.
Maybe then you will stop
staring at my castle, Osman Bey.
Did the Crusaders stop staring at my lands?
Why would I change my mind about Abranos?
They are not like us.
The bond we have with
horses is destiny's gift for us.
Westerners do not know how
to shoot arrows on a horse.
A few of them could do it but it was
impossible for them to do it as an army.
Until I, Imren Tegin took over. I did this.
Now I want you to see what
kind of army you will fight against.
You will have an army that
fights like you do, Osman Bey.
They will know your every
move and foresee your every trap.
You will see it when the field is set.
Let your men know about our dominance.
They have no chance against
my brave soldiers in the battlefield.
Brave soldiers? Like the alps behind you?
That's right.
Open the field.
Open it and let them see brave soldiers.
So you want to see your men's strength, is that so?
Let's see. We will see whose
dreams are closer to reality.
Turaham Come here.
-Come here.
-Three against one, is that so?
You're as delusional as they say, Osman Bey.
We will see.
We will see. Come on boy.
-The field is yours.
-Here.
Come on, Turahan!
Come on boy!
Praise be to my brave soldier!
Praise be!
My boy, thank you. Thank you.
Imren Tegin, or whatever you are,
Here, you've seen it.
We take our strength from the cause in our hearts.
That's what you're missing.
People behind us only follow
the path of our Creator.
What about yours? Mercenaries.
Looters, leaderless'...
How many more such skilled
soldiers do you have, Osman Bey?
A hundred? A thousand? Ten thousand?
We're talking about the Crusaders.
Neither your religion nor your
cause can save you in this battle.
Okay. I wanted to talk to you about Crusaders.
I thought you've brought my relics.
Not only relics.
-Osman.
-Now we can talk.
Let's get inside.
Let's talk in private..
Imren's men are coming, my Shahzade.
Everyone knows what to do.
Only one of them is precious for us.
We will destroy the rest of them.
Where is the gold that Olcaytu Khan promised?
-Deliver us the gold.
-You won't get what you hoped...
...you will get what you’ve found.
And that is the sharper side of our swords!
How dare you threaten Turks?
Allah is the Greatest!
Run away, dastard.
We will eventually catch you.
Demirboga,
Follow that dog.
We will learn the hidden
passages in the castle from him.
Yes, my Shahzade.
Now we will hunt you down, Imren Tegin. Alps!
Konur Bey is waiting for you.
Take the gold to them, come on.
Yes, my Shahzade.
And now you're taking my gold, is that so?
You're doing your best to
get yourself killed, Osman.
-And you’re standing against me.
-You're the one who brings the trouble.
I stand in front of people.
I’m the first to get in trouble.
Dying is nothing to me.
Is that so?
-The gold and relics can go to hell!
-Stop there.
You'll do as I say.
Otherwise I'll take everything
you have including your life.
You need to be equal to me...
...in order to bargain with me.
I took Kite from you. I'll give you
Germiyan's Frontier Marketplace,
and Olcaytu Khan's gold.
You will give the Frontier Marketplace, is that so?
It's not right to take something
without giving anything.
Just wait.
I haven't gotten anything yet.
You'll bargain with me first.
Forgive me brothers, we
need to take this marketplace.
May it be easy, alps. Be careful with it.
What's the matter, Konur Bey? Why did you come...
...to the frontier market without knowledge?
We seek no troubles, Kanyumaz.
Kanyumaz, we will take over the frontier market.
Stay back and obey Osman Bey's orders.
What are you talking about? Just go.
away. Or some blood will be shed here.
We have no intention to shed blood, Kanyumaz.
Turn the market over to us.
-Alps!
-Stop!
Stop! Alps, stop!
Brothers.
It's me! Cerkutay!
Cerkutay who protected you in this frontier market.
Do you remember?
Tajeddin Noyan!
...wanted to capture this
market and kill Osman Bey.
What did we do? We played
a great trick against him.
Our next move will be harder.
You trusted me.
Osman Bey...
...appreciates Germiyan alps as
much as he appreciates his own alps!
You believed me.
Believe me again.
Turn the frontier market over to us.
Cerkutay, get out of my way.
Kanyumaz, this is my final word.
you don't do as I say,
...both sides will lose too many.
And you will be responsible
for the blood shed here.
Alps, put your swords down.
Kanyumaz.
Alps will wait in the place we determine.
And people here will go back to their tribes.
-We've brought the gold safely.
-Thank you.
Now we'll wait for Imren Tegin's men.
Take positions accordingly, alps,
What do you want in return for my signs?
You won't let Crusaders come to my lands.
You shouldn't have built your
house on the way of Crusaders.
You shouldn't have lost your sings
You will figure something out.
You will make Crusaders pass
through the lands of Germiyan.
Yakup Bey... Yakup Bey is on campaign now.
They can't resist as strongly as we can.
They'll establish their
headquarters in Kutahya. So...
...Crusaders won’t be able to raid my lands.
When Crusaders leave,
...you will get your signs.
I see now. Devils are watching
you with admiration, Osman Bey.
You'll send Crusaders on
Yakup to get rid of him, huh?
I will do anything to protect my lands.
Don't be worrying.
I can do that. I will guide
Crusaders in these lands.
If you want the signs,
...do what I said.
Your soldiers will go to the frontier market.
They will capture both the market, and the gold.
Fine. What about Mehmed? Isn't he in
the palace? What will you do about him?
It's my concern.
-Welcome, Fitnat.
-Thank you, Gonca Hatun.
-What is that?
-Candaroglu has sent the dowry.
Saadet Hatun sends her regards.
We're going to the market.
Load these on the cart. Come on.
Come on.
Alaaddin.
Come on, Fitnat Hatun. Let's go.
-Let go of me.
-Move.
Aladdin.
Have you considered what I said, Trickster Hatun?
-Let's go talk to my father.
-You're dreaming, Alaaddin.
Nothing would change if we
saw him. He promised Candaroglu.
-He’ll never break his promise.
-Don't do this, Gonca.
I will convince my father.
I'll figure something out.
Alaaddin, there is no solution.
There's no way.
My brother would kill you.
And if he did, I couldn't stand it.
Orhan Bey gave up on Holofira for the state.
-Give up on me.
-No.
I won't give up on you, my hazel-eyed.
-I won't give up on you.
-Gonca Hatun.
-Mehmed Bey is coming.
-Alaaddin, just go.
Just go! Please just go.
-I said I wouldn’t go, Gonca.
Alaaddin f
Didn't I tell you not to get
close to my sister again?
She’s engaged now! Why don't you just get it?
-Mehmed, you are testing my patience!
-Brother, stop.
-I'm already out of patience.
Alps, arrest Mehmed Bey.
What are you talking about, Bala Hatun?
Sisters.
You arrest Gonca Hatun.
Take them to their rooms.
What does that mean, Bala Hatun?
You will be our guests for a while.
What game are you up to
again? You will pay for this!
-Mother, what's going on?
-Osman Bey's orders, son.
Listen to me carefully.
This war, Osman Bey, won't end before
either of us dies. Remember this.
It will end very soon. Don't be worrying.
It will finish between the
dogs behind you and my alps!
While your land's fate depends on my words,
...you are still challenging me.
I've ended the siege of Atronos.
You don't need to get in and out
through holes like a rat anymore.
Come through this gate like a man.
This is the first and last deal I've made with you.
Distract Crusaders and take the signs.
I will take them, Osman Bey. I will. Don’t worry.
Stay safe... Oh... I almost forgot.
Send my regards to Holofira and Olivia.
I’ll kill them too sooner or later.
When I want.
Lotus.
It's beautiful.
You know it lives in the water, right?
If you try to plant it, it dies.
I know.
And I do everything..
-..to keep it alive.
-Maybe this is the most beautiful death.
Being born in water and dying in your lover's soil.
I told you, Orhan.
Lillies live in water.
If you try to plant it in soil..
-..it dies.
-You told me.
You told me, Lord's daughter.
And I told you I will do anything..
..to keep it alive.
Now, I am the same Orhan, Holofira.
The Orhan that loves you.
Bey Orhan, Shahzade Orhan..
..the Orhan that had all
the solutions in his hand..
..but now is hopeless.
My Allah.
Keep us in the right path.
Alps! Pack up!
My Shahzade, I've lost track.
We will find it, those secret passages..
..will be the end of Rome's dog.
Come on!
Osman tricked us.
Brother. Hold it, just wait.
-We will learn when Osman Bey comes.
-What will we learn Gonca?
Osman sold us out. He went to Atranos.
He will make a deal with crusaders.
-Brother.
Osman Bey does not do such a thing.
You trust these Kayis more than us. Why Gonca, why?
I do not trust anyone. I watch
think and decide, brother.
Osman Bey only thinks for the benefit of Turks.
-He does not stab anyone in their back.
-Shut it.
You are blinded.
I am thinking if we are doing
a mistake father, however..
..no one else but that
Byzantinian girl could’ve done this.
Everything will be revealed at the court.
Do not overthink and muddle your mind.
-Elcim..
-Aunt..
My daughter Ayca.
-Ayca.
-Aunt.
-Go away!
-Aunt’
-No! Go away!
-What is it, my daughter!
Go and bring Alaeddin Bey at once!
My girl.
GERMIYANOGLU BORDER - FRONTIER MARKET
We can deliver the gold for the army
to Frontier Marketplace, however..
-..have a bad feeling about it.
-You are right, my brother.
Imren will grow his power
with Frontier Marketplace..
...and these gold.
Do not worry. Osman Bey..
..will not allow the infidel to have these gold.
-If Allah permits.
You do not have the intelligence
to calculate all these gold.
The dog of Imren Tegin.
It surprises me how you can even count goats.
Look here. Do you know how we learned calculations?
By counting the heads of the men we killed.
Watch your tongue while you still have your head.
It seems Imren Tegin has been soft on you.
Leave our marketplace..
..before we take your lives here.
..we will meet again.
Dani.. Daniel.
We will meet again.
However, at that time..
..swords will do the talking.
Alps, come on.
Her breath is stabilized.
-Her fever has gone down too.
-Then why isn't she awake?
My Allah, give her cure.
Ulgen Hatun, make her drink this.
-She will get up Gunduz Bey, I hope.
-In the name of Allah, the merciful, the compassionate.
-She is waking up.
-Aunt.
You are alright and will be better,
if Allah permits.
-What happened to me?
-You were poisoned, my girl.
You will be better.
Aunt?
-Stop!
-Let me go!
-Let me!
-Hold her tight Ulgen!
-I will kill myself!
-Hold her!
Do something, Alaeddin Bey!
-Her hand is not opening!
-Let me go!
-I will kill myself!
-Aunt, stop!
-Stay calm!
Stay calm.
-What was this, Alaeddin Bey?
-The poison causes this, Gunduz Bey.
It has disturbed her soul.
-She can do things she never did before.
-Will she stay like this?
Time will tell.
Tell me, what is the situation?
Ayca opened her eyes.
However, her condition is not good.
If I didn't know her, I would've
said she were someone else.
Her body is healing, my Bey. However,
the poison has disturbed her soul.
She will show anger for a while.
Until we find the person who did this,
we will have the same anger, Osman Bey.
Do not worry. Today,
justice will prevail if Allah permits.
Peace be upon you.
You let us visit the Madrasa of Yusuf.
Thank you Holofira Hatun.
-I wanted to thank you, actually.
But... why did you call it a
madrasa? What can you learn here?
Yusuf, peace be with him,
taught the truth and...
... the falsehood to many prisoners here.
Since then, this place has
been named Madrasa of Yusuf.
As for what will be learned...
...the value of life is taught
to those who aim to take it...
...the trust to those who betray...
...and the value of halal to
those who reach out to haram.
But what if a person already knows these things?
What if she is accused and thrown into prison...
...what will she learn?
-I told you...
Madrasa of Yusuf... Yusuf (PBUH) was also thrown
into prison because of false accusations.
He was innocent. But there were
things he needed to know and learn.
Patience and submission to Allah.
But if a person wants to submit to Allah..
...they must first know themselves.
To find oneself, one must give up on oneself.
The way to reach the truth
is to give up on oneself.
What remains if you give up on yourself?
Was there anything else except Him anyway?
Jesus Christ... He had also given up on himself..
...do you know that?
-I do.
Like all the prophets, he
prioritized his ummah over himself.
Even if there were those among
his ummah who betrayed him...
...he never gave up on submitting to Allah.
Now, if you want to find yourself in this prison...
...if you want to find your Allah...
...follow the path of the Prophets.
One never loses on that path.
May Allah be with you.
It's almost time. Almost.
The ruthless warriors of the Catalans
have already set up their headquarters.
Where are they? Why don't
you bring them to the castle?
Because the Frankish have not come yet.
-Benjamin.
-Yes, Imren Tegin.
The Frankish will arrive soon.
You will welcome them.
They will unite with Catalans.
I saw them on the battlefield.
I know how invincible they are.
When Catalans and Franks unite...
...they will be an army which cannot be defeated.
Then, Mamluk and Osman..
They will all kneel before us.
Sisters... Take Holofira..
...and Olivia Hatun.
Orhan! Neither I nor my niece would do
such a thing!
-Aykurt.
-We will wait for you at the door, my Shahzade.
Why are you running away from me?
You cannot help me. I don't
want you to help me anyway.
Don't you say.... "The finger
cut by sharia does not hurt."
-What are you saying, Holofira?
-Justice will be secured today.
We will bow down to our fate.
Look at me. Look at my face. My fate...
...you are my fate, Lord's daughter.
Don't worry now. Soon,
your innocence will be proven.
Once... I thought the same.
You were the joy of my heart.
But I woke up from that dream.
And you should also wake up.
I don't want to see you again.
Orhan... Forget me.
Attention! Osman Bey!
Olivia... Holofira..
Step forward.
Olivia... did you try to kill Elcim Hatun and...
...poison Ayca Hatun? Tell me.
Malhun Hatun asked me the same question, Osman Bey.
I did not poison Ayca Hatun.
Boran! -My Bey...
Whose ring is this?
-It is my ring.
But what does this prove?
The poison in it can prove many things.
Now tell me...
Where is that poison?
Then let me tell you.
Now... it is in Ayca Hatun's veins.
She is struggling with death.
Either one of you...
...put the poison in the water.
Osman Bey, I've been living like
a hostage since I got your palace.
I didn't leave the room
without your alps or your sisters.
I didn't go to that room. You
can ask Malhun Hatun if you want.
She's right, Osman Bey.
Sisters were with her all the time.
If someone saw her, tell us.
Holofira. Now tell me.
When I heard that they will get married...
..I couldn't control my anger.
I wanted to poison Elcim
Hatun but I poisoned Ayca Hatun.
I regret it, I wish I hadn't done it.
Murderer.
-You're a murderer.
-Daughter, no.
Just stop. This is not a right place for wrath.
Holofira. Tell me how you did it.
I knew there was poison in my aunt's ring.
She would take it out before sleep.
I took it and she didn’t realize.
I snuck into Elcim Hatun's room.
I poured the poison in her water.
Your confession...
...and your crime coincide.
Is there anything else you want to say?
Holofira wanted to kill Elcim Hatun...
...but she ended up poison!ng Ayca Hatun.
Tell me Elcim Hatun, do you have something to say?
Forgive me for doubting your justice, Osman Bey.
I want to say that...
...Holofira said that she regretted it,
and thankfully my sister in law did not die.
I don't want her to...
...die.
I want her banished so she cannot
come to these lands again
What about you, Gunduz Bey?
Do you have anything to say?
After my daughter’s mercy, I have nothing to say.
-Then...
-Stop.
I haven't talked yet.
-Ayca
-Yenge? (Sister in law)
Forgive me, Osman Bey. I interrupted you.
I have my right to retaliation.
I will not forgive this
ignoble daughter of lord's.
I want my right to retaliate.
Ayca Hatun, is this your final decision?
This is what the justice requires, mercy...
...is a holiday for the merciless.
I want my right to retaliate.
I'm declaring my decision.
Holofira wanted to kill Elcim Hatun
and poisoned Ayca Hatun.
She said she regretted it,
but her regret...
...isn't enough
for the victim's mercy.
So...
She will pay for...
...what she did.
She will be executed with the water...
...that she poisoned Ayca Hatun.
There is life in retaliation.
May my Creator forgive your sins.
Forgive me.
Holofira.
Justice has finally been served.
Thankfully.
I wish this hadn't happened.
But you reap what you sow.
It was a tough matter, Osman Bey.
Gunduz Bey!
The important thing...
...is to see behind the invisible...
May my Creator illuminate us.
My Bey, the pioneer troop of Crusaders is coming.
Their route leads to Sudibi.
It leads to Sudibi, is that so?
Then they will unite with
the others. If they unite,
it will be pretty hard to separate them.
Alps!
Prepare the horses.
These lands are home to those
who come as a friend...
...and a grave for those who come with enmity.
Let them come.
We have lots of land!
We'll bury them all in this land,
if Allah permits!
Visit turkision.com for more!